const dayFourteenQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Who was the first ransom in Islam?",
    options: [
      "Abu Bakr Sidiq",
      "Umar bn Khattab",
      "Uthman bn ‘Affan",
      "Ali bn Abi Talib",
      "Mus’ab bn ‘Umayr",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "When was the death of Aisha bint Abubakr (May Allaah be pleased with her and her father)?",
    options: ["63 AH", "57 AH", "53 AH", "60 AH", "65 AH"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who were the three companions that Allaah is referring to in Suratul Tawbah (verse 118) for non-participation during battle of Tabuk?",
    options: [
      "Ka’b bn Malik, Hilal bn Umayyah and Marwan bn Rabi’",
      "Ka’b bn Malik, ‘Abdullah bn Maslul and Marwan bn Rabi’",
      "Ka’b bn Malik, Hilal bn Umayyah and ‘Abdullah bn Maslul",
      "‘Abdullah bn Maslul, Hilal bn Umayyah and Marwan bn Rabi’",
      "Ka’b bn Malik, Hilal bn Umayyah and Amru bn ‘Aas",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who is the Companion that the Prophet Muhammad (May the peace and blessing of Allaah be upon him) named Gaseelu-l-Malaikah (who was washed by Angels after he was put killed)?",
    options: [
      "Mus’ab bn ‘Umayr",
      "Simak bn Kharasha",
      "Khudhayfah bn Yamani",
      "Hanzalah bn Abi ‘Aamir",
      "Sa’du bn Abi Waqas Azzuhri",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the real name of Abu Hurairah (May Allaah be pleased with him), the great companion?",
    options: [
      "'Abdullah bn Zubair",
      "Salman al-Faarisiy",
      "'Abdur Rahman bn Sakhra Ad Dusiy",
      "'Abdullah bn Sakhra Ad Dusiy",
      "Salman bn 'Abdullah al-Faarisiy",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Who among the Arabs first threw an arrow in the cause of Allah?",
    options: [
      "Mus’ab bn ‘Umayr",
      "Simak bn Kharasha",
      "Khudhayfah bn Yamani",
      "Hanzalah bn Abi ‘Aamir",
      "Sa’du bn Abi Waqas Azzuhri",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "‘Jabir’ said: He heard the Prophet saying “The Throne of Beneficent shakes because of the death of ……………",
    options: [
      "Mus’ab bn ‘Umayr",
      "Sa’du bn Mu’adh",
      "Khudhayfah bn Yamani",
      "Hanzalah bn Abi ‘Aamir",
      "Sa’du bn Abi Waqas Azzuhri",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who was the first Adhan among the companion of the messenger of Allah?",
    options: [
      "Ka’b bn Malik",
      "‘Abdullah bn Umm Makktum",
      "Bilal bn Robah",
      "Hilal bn Umayyah",
      "Marwan bn Rabi’",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who stabbed Aliy bn Abi Talib (May Allaah be pleased with him), the great companion?",
    options: [
      "Abu Luhluati Almajusiy",
      "‘Abdullahi bn Maslul",
      "Ubayi bn Khalaf",
      "Ja’sh bn Ubal",
      "‘Abdur Rahman bn Muljama",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "When was the death of Abubakr sidiq (May Allaah be pleased with him), the great companion?",
    options: ["9 AH", "10 AH", "11 AH", "12 AH", "13 AH"],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the real name of Abi Ayuub al-ansariy (May Allaah be pleased with him), the great companion?",
    options: [
      "Khalid bn Zayd bn Kulayb bn Tha’labah",
      "Arqam bn Abi Arqam",
      "Zayd bn Harith",
      "‘Amar bn Yasir",
      "Zayd bn Abi Waqas",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who died last amongst Prophet Muhammad (May the peace and blessing of Allaah be upon him)’s wives?",
    options: [
      "Ummu Salamah Hind bint Abi Umayyah",
      "‘Aishah bint Abibakr",
      "Zainab bint Jahsh",
      "Saodah bint Zam’ah",
      "Juwairiyah bint Harith",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who among the companions, said: “I am the one that my mother named Haydarah”?",
    options: [
      "Hamza bn ‘Abdil Mutallib",
      "Khalid bn Walid",
      "‘Umar bn Khattab",
      "‘Ali bn Abi Talib",
      "‘Amar bn Yasir",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who was the companion that the Prophet asked to learn Jewish Language, and he learnt it within 15 days?",
    options: [
      "Khalid bn Zayd bn Kulayb bn Tha’labah",
      "Zaydu bn Thabit",
      "Zayd bn Harith",
      "‘Amar bn Yasir",
      "Zayd bn Abi Waqas",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who was the lady referred to in this verse of Quran: “Indeed Allaah has heard the statement of her that disputed with you (Muhammad) concerning her husband….”Q58:1?",
    options: [
      "Ummu Sulaim",
      "Asmau bint Abibakr",
      "Sumayyah Ummu ‘Ammar bn Yasir",
      "Khadijat bint Khuwailid",
      "Khaolah bint Tha’labah",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
];

export default dayFourteenQuestions;
